Frank A. Johnson Papers
Frank A. Johnson Papers
- Production
  - Business transactions
    - Banner Slipper Co., 1950; 1952,; 1963 (Box 31)
    - Bata Shoe Co., 1946-1949; 1951,; 1954,; 1961 (Box 31)
    - Beck Shoe Corp., 1956 (Box 31)
    - Bennett Ltd., 1940-1949; 1951,; 1953; See Production: Related material: Permacounter: Bennett Ltd.
    - H. R. Bliss Co., Inc., 1930 (Box 31)
    - British Rubber Co. of Canada, Ltd., 1946-1950; 1952-1954,; 1964 (Box 31)
    - Brockton Cutting Die and Machine Co., 1946; See Production: Related material: Permacounter: Brockton Cut Sole Corp.
    - Brown Shoe Co., 1953; 1956,; 1961,; undated (Box 31)
    - Brown, H. H. Shoe Co.,Inc., 1945-1956; 1958 (Box 31)
    - Cadre Industries, 1958; 1961 (Box 31)
    - Cambridge Rubber Co., 1943-1963 (Box 31)
    - Caplan, Sidney Ltd., 1956 (Box 31)
    - Central Counter Co., 1961 (Box 31)
    - Cleveland Slipper and Shoe Co., 1950 (Box 31)
    - Commonwealth Services, Inc., 1959 (Box 31)
    - Continental Can Co., 1962 (Box 31)
    - Collingwood Shoe Co., 1930 (Box 31)
    - Colonial Tanning Co., 1953; 1954,; 1956-1958 (Box 31)
    - Compo Shoe Machinery Corp., 1950-1955; 1960,; 1961 (Box 31)
    - Consolidated Moulded Products Corp., 1956 (Box 31)
    - Dewey and Almy Chemical Co., 1945-1949; 1951,; 1958,; 1961 (Box 31)
    - Drexage, L & Co., 1946; 1947 (Box 31)
    - Dupont Denemours and Co., 1954; 1955,; 1961,; 1963; See Production: Related material: Permacounter: E. I. DuPont DeNemours & Co.
    - Eberle Tanning Co., 1949; 1956-1958 (Box 32)
    - Empire Specialty Footwear Co., 1949 (Box 32)
    - Erie Railroad Co., 1947 (Box 32)
    - Export and Import Co., 1945-1949; 1951,; 1958,; 1960,; 1961 (Box 32)
    - Family Shoe Store, 1950 (Box 32)
    - The Felters Co., 1946; 1951,; 1956,; 1962,; 1963 (Box 32)
    - Flex-Mor Shoe Co., 1958; 1961 (Box 32)
    - Louis G. Freeman Co., 1937-1941; 1944,; 1948,; 1949,; 1953,; 1963 (Box 32)
    - Gair, Robert Co., 1930; 1945,; 1948-1950 (Box 32)
    - General Electric, 1957-1959 (Box 32)
    - General Shoe Corp, 1946; 1949,; 1952-1955,; 1958-1961; Genesso (Box 32)
    - Goodyear Shoe Co., 1953; 1954 (Box 32)
    - Grant, W. T. Co., 1946-1950; 1959,; 1961,; 1963 (Box 32)
    - Haley-Cate-Rockwood Co., 1930 (Box 32)
    - Hankins Container Co., 1950; 1951,; 1957,; 1960 (Box 32)
    - Harwick Standard Chemical, 1957 (Box 32)
    - Jos M. Herman Shoe Co., 1959 (Box 32)
    - Hebert L. Hill Co., 1930 (Box 32)
    - Howard Warehouse Terminals, Inc., 1954; 1955,; 1956,; 1959 (Box 32)
    - Hurd Shoe Co., 1960 (Box 32)
    - I. B. M. Corp., 1947; 1956-1960,; 1962,; 1963,; undated (Box 32)
    - Ideal Tool and Machine Co., 1955; 1958 (Box 33)
    - International Shoe Co., 1930; 1957,; 1959,; 1960,; 1962 (Box 33)
    - International Shoe Machine Corp., 1946; 1947,; 1950,; 1953,; 1956,; 1959,; 1961 (Box 33)
    - Jenkins, George O. Co., 1946; 1947,; 1949,; 1951,; undated (Box 33)
    - Kenworthy Brothers Co., 1944; 1946,; 1947,; 1949-1952 (Box 33)
    - Keystone State Shoe Co. subsidiary-Tunkhannock Shoe Co., 1945-1953; 1957 (Box 33)
    - Lawrence Processing Co., 1953-1956 (Box 33)
    - Leather Co., 1930; 1949,; 1961,; undated (Box 33)
    - Louis Lefkowitz & Brothers, 1930 (Box 33)
    - Link Aviation, 1955; 1957,; 1958,; 1963,; 1964 (Box 33)
    - Logan Co., 1930; 1947 (Box 33)
    - MacDonald Manufacturing Co., 1955 (Box 33)
    - Madison Shoe Co., 1930 (Box 33)
    - Manufacturers Supplies Co., 1946-1958; 1962 (Box 33)
    - Markem Machine Co., 1950; 1951 (Box 33)
    - May Co., 1961 (Box 33)
    - McLean Wood-Mosaic Co.,Inc., 1954-1960 (Box 33)
    - Merker Counter Co., 1945; 1946,; 1948,; 1951,; 1957,; 1958 (Box 33)
    - P. W. Minor and Son, Inc., 1959 (Box 33)
    - Mohawk Airlines, Inc., 1957; 1958,; 1965 (Box 33)
    - Monsanto Chemical Co., 1953; 1954,; undated (Box 34)
    - Montgomery Ward, 1947; 1952-1954,; 1956-1960 (Box 34)
    - National Foot Health Council, 1957; 1958 (Box 34)
    - National Shoe Board Conference, Inc., 1943-1946; 1948,; 1951,; 1952 (Box 34)
    - National Shoe Institute, 1957-1959; 1962 (Box 34)
    - National Shoe Products Corp., 1955-1958 (Box 34)
    - New York Telephone Co., 1953; 1956,; 1957,; 1959 (Box 34)
    - North American Leasing Co., Inc., 1955 (Box 34)
    - Outdoorsmen Shoemakers, Inc., 1958; 1959 (Box 34)
    - Plymouth Cordage Industries, 1957; 1958,; 1960,; 1961 (Box 34)
    - Plymouth Machinery Co., 1961; 1962 (Box 34)
    - Premier Thread Co., 1958 (Box 34)
    - Putney, Stephen Shoe Co., 1941; 1942,; 1944,; 1945,; 1948,; 1950 (Box 34)
    - Raymond Corp., The, 1957 (Box 34)
    - Reliable Leather Pigment Finish Co., 1961; 1962 (Box 34)
    - Reyam Plastic Products Co., 1947 (Box 34)
    - Richland Davidson Shoe Co., 1954 (Box 34)
    - Robin Footwear Corp., 1961 (Box 34)
    - Ro-Search, Inc., 1957-1959 (Box 34)
    - Rossendale Ruboil Co., 1930 (Box 34)
    - Rubatex Products, Inc., 1960; 1961 (Box 34)
    - Rubber companies, 1947-1949; 1959,; 1961,; 1963,; 1965 (Box 34)
    - Safety First Shoe Co., 1955; 1959 (Box 35)
    - G. L. Salinger & Associates, 1954; 1955 (Box 35)
    - Sandler of Boston, 1946-1949; 1952,; 1957 (Box 35)
    - Savage Shoe Co., Ltd., 1948 (Box 35)
    - Scoville Manufacturing, 1953 (Box 35)
    - Sears Roebuck & Co.
      - 1941, 1946, 1948-1950 (Box 35)
      - 1957-1959 (Box 35)
    - Shoe Corporation of Canada, 1957-1959 (Box 35)
    - Skippy Footwear Corp., 1956 (Box 35)
    - Slater's Boot Shops, Inc., 1955; 1957 (Box 35)
    - Snell-Jones Tack Corp., 1946; 1947,; 1950 (Box 35)
    - Snyder's Wood Heel Co., Inc., 1930 (Box 35)
    - Southern Heel Co., 1962 (Box 35)
    - Southern Latex Corp., 1949; 1951 (Box 35)
    - Superior Fibre Co., The, 1955 (Box 35)
    - Swedish Shoe Industries (Box 35)
    - Texon, Inc., 1953 (Box 35)
    - Transportation Association of America, 1958 (Box 35)
    - Triple Cities Heel Co., 1947 (Box 35)
    - Tubular Rivet and Stud Co., 1946 (Box 35)
    - Union Plastics Corp., 1948; undated (Box 36)
    - United Last Co., 1949; 1950 (Box 36)
    - United Shoe Machinery Corp.
      - 1944, 1945 (Box 36)
      - 1946 (Box 36)
      - 1947, 1948 (Box 36)
      - 1948, 1949 (Box 36)
    - United States Rubber Co., 1943; 1945-1949,; 1951,; 1957-1959,; undated (Box 36)
    - United States Shoe Corp., 1955 (Box 36)
    - Vulcan Last Corp., 1930; 1944-1945,; 1946-1949,; 1957-1962 (Box 36)
    - Vylyt Corp., 1959 (Box 36)
    - Worcester Shoe Co., 1953-1958 (Box 36)
- Published material
  - Newspaper clippings
    - About Endicott, N. Y., 1956 (Box 37)
    - Election of Frank A. Johnson to presidency of Endicott-Johnson Corp., 1956; 1957 (Box 37)
    - Endicott-Johnson Queen, 1960 (Box 37)
    - Messages, 1960 (Box 37)